♪ ♪
♪ COME ON, BABY ♪
♪ LET'S DO THE TWIST ♪
♪ TAKE ME BY MY LITTLE HAND ♪
♪ AND GO LIKE THIS ♪
♪ ♪
♪ E-YAH, TWIST ♪
♪ BABY, BABY, TWIST ♪
♪ ♪
♪ OOH YEAH, JUST LIKE THIS ♪
♪ COME ON, LITTLE MISS,
AND DO THE TWIST ♪
♪ ♪
♪ MY DADDY IS SLEEPIN' ♪
♪ AND MAMA AIN'T AROUND ♪
♪ ♪
♪ YEAH, DADDY JUST SLEEPIN' ♪
♪ AND MAMA AIN'T AROUND ♪
♪ ♪
♪ WE'RE GONNA TWISTY,
TWISTY, TWISTY ♪
♪ 'TIL WE TEAR THE HOUSE DOWN ♪
♪ ♪
♪ COME ON AND TWIST ♪
♪ YEAH, BABY, TWIST ♪
♪ ♪
♪ OOH YEAH, JUST LIKE THIS ♪
♪ COME ON, LITTLE MISS,
AND DO THE TWIST ♪
♪ ♪
♪ E-YAH ♪
♪ ('ROUND AND 'ROUND
AND 'ROUND AND 'ROUND) ♪
♪ ♪
♪ ('ROUND AND 'ROUND AND
'ROUND AND 'ROUND) ♪
♪ ♪
♪ ('ROUND AND 'ROUND
AND 'ROUND AND 'ROUND) ♪
♪ YEAH, YOU SHOULD
SEE MY LITTLE SIS ♪
♪ ♪
♪ YOU SHOULD SEE MY,
MY LITTLE SIS ♪
♪ ♪
♪ SHE REALLY KNOWS HOW TO ROCK ♪
♪ SHE KNOWS HOW TO TWIST ♪
♪ ♪
♪ COME ON AND TWIST ♪
♪ YEAH, BABY TWIST ♪
♪ ♪
♪ OOH YEAH, JUST LIKE THIS ♪
♪ COME ON, LITTLE MISS,
AND DO THE TWIST ♪
♪ ('ROUND AND 'ROUND
AND 'ROUND AND 'ROUND) ♪
♪ YEAH ♪
♪ ('ROUND AND 'ROUND
AND 'ROUND AND 'ROUND) ♪
♪ THAT'S ALL NOW ♪
♪ ('ROUND AND 'ROUND
AND 'ROUND AND 'ROUND) ♪
♪ YEAH, TWIST ALL NIGHT ♪
♪ ♪
♪ TWIST ♪
♪ ('ROUND AND 'ROUND
AND 'ROUND) ♪